{
    "exam_metadata": {
        "layout": "exam",
        "title": "Practice Exam 14",
        "exam_id": 14,
        "courseName": "AWS Cloud Practitioner",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "tags": [
            "aws",
            "cloud"
        ],
        "description": "Introduction exam"
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing model can provide discounts of up to 90%?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Spot Instances",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Hosts"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Spot Instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question_text": "What is the AWS customer responsible for according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Data encryption",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Physical access controls"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Data encryption"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Secure disposal of storage devices"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Environmental risk management"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS Cloud services can be used to run a customer-managed relational database?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon ElastiCache"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon DynamoDB"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question_text": "A company is looking for a scalable data warehouse solution. <br/> Which of the following AWS solutions would meet the company's needs?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Redshift",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon DynamoDB"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Kinesis"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Redshift"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question_text": "Which statement best describes Elastic Load Balancing?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It translates a domain name into an IP address using DNS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It collects metrics on connected Amazon EC2 instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It automatically adjusts the number of Amazon EC2 instances to support incoming traffic."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question_text": "Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Command line interface | Software Development Kits",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Command line interface"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "On-premises"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Software Development Kits"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Software-as-a-service"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Hybrid"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question_text": "The AWS Cloud's multiple Regions are an example of:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "global infrastructure.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "agility."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "global infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "elasticity."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "pay-as-you-go pricing."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon S3 | Amazon CloudFront",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Storage Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question_text": "Web servers running on Amazon EC2 access a legacy application running in a corporate data center. <br/> What term would describe this model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Hybrid architecture",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Cloud-native"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Partner network"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Hybrid architecture"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Infrastructure as a service"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question_text": "What is the benefit of using AWS managed services, such as Amazon ElastiCache and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "They simplify patching and updating underlying OSs.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "They require the customer to monitor and replace failing instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "They have better performance than customer-managed services."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "They simplify patching and updating underlying OSs."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "They do not require the customer to optimize instance type or size selections."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question_text": "Which service provides a virtually unlimited amount of online highly durable object storage?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon S3",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Redshift"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question_text": "Which of the following Identity and Access Management (IAM) entities is associated with an access key ID and secret access key when using AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "IAM user",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "IAM group"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "IAM user"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "IAM role"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "IAM policy"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question_text": "Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks | Data encryption",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Multi-factor authentication physical tokens"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Data encryption"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Automated penetration testing"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question_text": "Which AWS managed service is used to host databases?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon RDS",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Batch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a simple and scalable shared file storage solution for use with Linux-based AWS and on-premises servers?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EFS",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EFS"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question_text": "When architecting cloud applications, which of the following are a key design principle?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Implement elasticity",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Use the largest instance possible"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Provision capacity for peak load"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use the Scrum development process"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Implement elasticity"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service should be used for long-term, low-cost storage of data backups?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Glacier",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS EBS"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question_text": "Which task is AWS responsible for in the shared responsibility model for security and compliance?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Encrypting data in transit",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Granting access to individuals and services"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Encrypting data in transit"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Updating Amazon EC2 host firmware"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Updating operating systems"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question_text": "Where should a company go to search software listings from independent software vendors to find, test, buy and deploy software that runs on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Marketplace",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Marketplace"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Lumberyard"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudSearch"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is a benefit of using the AWS Cloud?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ability to focus on revenue-generating activities.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Permissive security removes the administrative burden."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Ability to focus on revenue-generating activities."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Control over cloud network hardware."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Choice of specific cloud hardware vendors."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question_text": "When performing a cost analysis that supports physical isolation of a customer workload, which compute hosting model should be accounted for in the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Dedicated Hosts",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Dedicated Hosts"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "No Upfront Reserved Instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides the ability to manage infrastructure as code?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CloudFormation",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodePipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeDeploy"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question_text": "If a customer needs to audit the change management of AWS resources, which of the following AWS services should the customer use?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Config",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question_text": "What is Amazon CloudWatch?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "A metrics repository with customizable notification thresholds and channels.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "A code repository with customizable build and team commit features."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "A metrics repository with customizable notification thresholds and channels."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "A security configuration repository with threat analytics."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "A rule repository of a web application firewall with automated vulnerability prevention features."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question_text": "Which service allows a company with multiple AWS accounts to combine its usage to obtain volume discounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Server Migration Service"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question_text": "Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS OpsWorks | AWS CodeDeploy",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS OpsWorks"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeDeploy"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Batch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model adjusts based on supply and demand of EC2 instances?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Spot Instances",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "On-Demand Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Spot Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Convertible Reserved Instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question_text": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Implement loose coupling. | Design for scalability.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Use manual monitoring."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use fixed servers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Implement loose coupling."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Rely on individual components."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Design for scalability."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question_text": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that allows for one-hour target response time for support cases?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Business",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Developer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Basic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question_text": "Where can AWS compliance and certification reports be downloaded?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Artifact",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Concierge"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Certificate Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a customized view of the health of specific AWS services that power a customer's workloads running on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Health Dashboard"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an advantage of consolidated billing on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Volume pricing qualification",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Volume pricing qualification"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Shared access permissions"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Multiple bills per account"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Eliminates the need for tagging"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question_text": "Which of the following steps should be taken by a customer when conducting penetration testing on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Request and wait for approval from AWS support, and then conduct testing.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Conduct penetration testing using Amazon Inspector, and then notify AWS support."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Request and wait for approval from the customer's internal security team, and then conduct testing."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Notify AWS support, and then conduct testing immediately."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Request and wait for approval from AWS support, and then conduct testing."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS features enables a user to launch a pre-configured Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Machine Image",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Machine Image"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Systems Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon AppStream 2.0"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question_text": "How would an AWS customer easily apply common access controls to a large set of users?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM group.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM group."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM role."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Apply the same IAM policy to all IAM users with access to the same workload."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Apply an IAM policy to an Amazon Cognito user pool."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question_text": "Which AWS Cost Management tool allows you to view the most granular data about your AWS bill?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Cost and Usage report",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost and Usage report"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Billing dashboard"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question_text": "Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CloudFormation | AWS Management Console",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Concierge"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS Management Console"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an AWS Cloud architecture design principle?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Implement loose coupling.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Implement single points of failure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Implement loose coupling."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Implement monolithic design."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Implement vertical scaling."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question_text": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users. | Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Enable AWS CloudTrail."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question_text": "Which service provides a hybrid storage service that enables on-premises applications to seamlessly use cloud storage?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Storage Gateway",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Storage Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Block Storage (Amazon EBS)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question_text": "Which of the following services falls under the responsibility of the customer to maintain operating system configuration, security patching, and networking?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon ElastiCache"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Fargate"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an important architectural design principle when designing cloud applications?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Use multiple Availability Zones.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Use multiple Availability Zones."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use tightly coupled components."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use open source software."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Provision extra capacity."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question_text": "Which AWS support plan includes a dedicated Technical Account Manager?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Enterprise",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Developer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Enterprise"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Business"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Basic"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question_text": "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) offers which of the following benefits over traditional database management?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS manages the maintenance of the operating system.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS manages the data stored in Amazon RDS tables."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS manages the maintenance of the operating system."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS automatically scales up instance types on demand."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS manages the database type."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question_text": "Which service is best for storing common database query results, which helps to alleviate database access load?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon ElastiCache",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Machine Learning"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon SQS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon ElastiCache"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 Instance Store"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is a component of the shared responsibility model managed entirely by AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Auditing physical data center assets",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Patching operating system software"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Encrypting data"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Enforcing multi-factor authentication"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Auditing physical data center assets"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question_text": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Online Tech Talks | AWS Classroom Training",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Online Tech Talks"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Blog"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Forums"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS Classroom Training"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question_text": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard? (Select TWO.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Security Groups | Subnets",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront distributions"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Security Groups"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Subnets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Elastic Load Balancing"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question_text": "If each department within a company has its own AWS account, what is one way to enable consolidated billing?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Create an AWS Organization from the payer account and invite the other accounts to join.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Use AWS Budgets on each account to pay only to budget."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Contact AWS Support for a monthly bill."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Create an AWS Organization from the payer account and invite the other accounts to join."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Put all invoices into one Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket, load data into Amazon Redshift, and then run a billing report."
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}